[{"answer": "my friend, can't you incorporate one unselfish act in your daily routine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And I'm going to have an English muffin with margarine on the side and a cup of coffee", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, c'mon! It's down again?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh, I can't believe it. Let me see that.  That's four and a half points in three days! That's almost half my money", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh, I can't believe it. Let me see that.  That's four and a half points in three days! That's almost half my money", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Yeah, you told me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Hey, where.. where are you going? You gonna take a trip? The map.. what.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Hey, can I use your place? I got a bunch of friends coming over this weekend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "All my friend was able to find out is that he's in the hospital", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Of course he's been in touch with him. He's left two messages. He just hasn't heard back yet, that's all", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Where", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The hospital", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What are you, a doctor", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Today. I'm going today. Just don't do anything until you hear from me", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah, and you're just what she's looking for too", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What? What? Did you go down there?  Did he tell you what's gonna happen?  How long were you there", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Not especially", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What can we do? It's raining", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I did. I'm just curious. It's been almost a week. I want to check it out.  Six points. It's up six points", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You did not tell me not to sell", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "They're very clean animals", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Stock-Tip.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Almost as bad as losing out to a perfume", "qsentId": 22}]